<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs.atom"/>
  <title>Ez Detangler Brush - EZ Blogs</title>
  <updated>2020-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Ez Detangler Brush</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs/how-to-fix-the-damaged-curly-hair</id>
    <published>2020-02-28T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-05-23T03:13:34-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs/how-to-fix-the-damaged-curly-hair"/>
    <title>How to fix the damaged curly hair?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Aniyah S. Brown</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>If you are looking for damaged curly hair treatment, there are a few things that you may want to consider to be able to bring your damaged hair back to life very quickly.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs/how-to-fix-the-damaged-curly-hair">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[So what Causes Damage to Curly Hair? Before figuring out how to repair your hair, you must first identify the cause of the damage. While some culprits are obvious, like heat and coloring chemicals, others can fly under the radar.
<p><span>Sometimes, things like rough detangling, over-styling, or harsh weather can cause wear and tear on your hair over time. </span></p>
<div align="justify"></div>
<div align="center"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0263/2764/6287/files/ezgif.com-gif-maker_4_697deaba-96a3-41dd-8332-972037df4467_large.gif?v=1568746991" alt=""></div>
<div align="justify"></div>
<div align="justify">
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Curly hair has its own needs, different from other hair types. Using the right products is essential to making sure that your curls are getting everything they need. While it’s easy to get caught up in trying to achieve “perfect curls,” it’s important that what you’re putting in your hair is doing more than just making it look good.</span></p>
<p><span>What your curls need most is MOISTURE! This is what helps them grow and adds shine and definition. Look for products that’ll hydrate your hair and are free of harmful and drying ingredients.</span></p>
</div>
<div align="justify"></div>
<div align="justify"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0263/2764/6287/files/photo-1558990397-489e8f26f88c_large.jpeg?v=1565653989" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></div>
<div align="justify"></div>
<p> <br>Detangling properly with the right tools and the products is the first step to liven up those sexy curls. Wrong detangling brushes can cause breakage that leads to split ends and we know how that plays out. Pick up our <a href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/products/the-ez-detangler-hair-brush" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">EZ Brush</a> and give it a shot with your favorite detangling products, you will be surprised we promise. You can check out how to properly use our brush right <a href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs/why-should-you-own-an-ez-detangler-brush" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.  </p>
<p><strong>Trust The Process:</strong></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>The most important thing is to trust the process. </span><span>Whether you’ve damaged your curls from straightening your hair or bleaching too often, it’ll take time for your hair to start bouncing back – healthy hair doesn’t happen overnight!</span><span> You just have to treat it well and be patient, and slowly but surely you’ll see that your curls will thank you for it</span></p>
<div align="justify"></div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs/why-should-you-own-an-ez-detangler-brush</id>
    <published>2020-01-08T01:30:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-05-23T03:01:32-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs/why-should-you-own-an-ez-detangler-brush"/>
    <title>Why should you own an EZ Detangler Brush?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Aniyah S. Brown</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[All brands out there will tell you they have the best brush, but we took on this challenge and delivered. We looked at the design and saw a few simple tweaks we could make to make it versatile enough for all of you. So go ahead experience the new dawn of detangling<p><a class="read-more" href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs/why-should-you-own-an-ez-detangler-brush">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Many years ago, when I was a cosmetology student, we were given this<span> </span><a href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/products/the-ez-detangler-hair-brush">detangling brush</a>. EZ Detangler Brush is used for detangling and teasing hair. Even after TWO years, this brush is still in perfect shape. I underestimated the value of this brush until I decided to stop getting chemical relaxers. Before then, I hardly used it. My natural hair is much easier to detangle utilizing this brush.</p>
<figure class="wp-block-embed-youtube wp-block-embed is-type-rich wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio">
<div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper"><span class="embed-youtube"><iframe class="youtube-player" type="text/html" width="825" height="465" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/yA4aD4ZdNEY?version=3&amp;rel=1&amp;fs=1&amp;autohide=2&amp;showsearch=0&amp;showinfo=1&amp;iv_load_policy=1&amp;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true"></iframe></span></div>
</figure>
<p><strong>How to use an EZ Brush to detangle hair?</strong></p>
<p>There are many uses for the EZ Brush; however, I use it to detangle my naturally curly hair mainly. Every time I wet my hair, whether it is to detangle or style, I use this brush. The plastic bristles protect my hair as I work through the knots and tangles. Here are the steps that I use to get tangle-free hair.</p>
<ol type="1">
<li>Cleanse hair in the shower with a sulfate-free shampoo and our <a href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/collections/curlyqueen/products/acupuncture-scalp-massage-brush?variant=31104672956495" target="_blank" title="EZ Scalp Massage Brush" rel="noopener noreferrer">EZ Scalp Massage Brush</a>. This will help massage the scalp and wash hair correctly.</li>
<li>Then I use a generous amount of conditioner, and I saturate every strand in preparation for detangling.</li>
<li>Beginning at the hair ends, I gently work the tangles out, moving up to the root.</li>
<li>If your hair is not too messy and tangled, you can brush your hair before washing your hair. It will leave your hair manageable after a shower.</li>
</ol>
<p><strong>Define Curls with an EZ Brush</strong></p>
<p>Defining curls with the EZ is easy. This brush can detangle and separate curls for a more polished look. Tame frizz by smoothing the hair with the back of the EZ brush. As you work through the tangles, turn down your wrist as if you were using a curling iron. Use your favorite gel or mousse to get a longer-lasting curl.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0263/2764/6287/files/ezgif.com-gif-maker_11_large.gif?v=1576413644" alt=""></p>
<p>Investing in the proper tools for detangling hair is essential. Many people don’t know how to take care of curly hair and manage it. They choose a ton of products and invest without knowing anything about the product. However, for managing hair properly, nothing but a detangler brush is enough. And the EZ Detangler brush can meet all of your needs quickly for managing hair.</p>
<p>The main reason for the popularity of this brush is it is reasonably priced and also lasts for quite a long time. A detangling brush can support you for years. Moreover, you can also enjoy tangle-free hair anytime and anywhere. So, say bye-bye to the messy hair and hello to beautiful curly queen goodness</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs/detangling-simplified</id>
    <published>2019-12-04T23:40:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-05-23T03:23:28-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs/detangling-simplified"/>
    <title>You are Natural - You are Confident &amp; Beautiful</title>
    <author>
      <name>Aniyah S. Brown</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Detangling brush are just that, they help you detangle. So if you are going to buy one go ahead give us a shot, we will go over why we should be your first choice, right here.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/blogs/ez-blogs/detangling-simplified">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<div class="post-outer">
<div class="post">
<div class="post-body entry-content float-container" id="post-body-3000342480450179272">
<div>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<span>t can be hard for women to leave behind the protective styling, extensions and relaxers that they have been taught they need. When a woman begins the process of growing out and embracing her natural curls, there can be a lot of worries and considerations. Could they lose their jobs over their choice to wear their natural curls?</span>
</div>
<div><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0263/2764/6287/files/pexels-photo-2703316_large.jpeg?v=1586701622" alt="" width="440" height="293" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></div>
<div>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<span>Will they face questions, ridicule, or be targeted by others in stores or on the streets? Will their friends and families accept their new, natural look? All of these things can weigh heavily into a woman's decision about wearing her natural curls.</span>
</div>
<div></div>
<div>Times are changing, so many brushes out there today that make going natural easier than ever. There are all kinds of hairbrushes to choose from. There are those that are made to be part of a blow dryer so you can curl your hair as you dry it giving your hairstyle more body and lift. If you have thick curly hair an<span> </span><a href="https://ezdetanglerbrush.com/products/the-ez-detangler-hair-brush">EZ detangler brush</a><span> </span>also helps control the unruliness of curly hair.</div>
<div></div>
<div class="separator" style="text-align: center;"><iframe width="320" height="266" class="YOUTUBE-iframe-video" data-thumbnail-src="https://i.ytimg.com/vi/aA_S9AgVtr8/0.jpg" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/aA_S9AgVtr8?feature=player_embedded" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></div>
<div></div>
<div>
<p>However, despite these worries and concerns, many curlies find that wearing their natural curls can be empowering and liberating. In addition to spending less time and money at the salon on services, they are afforded the opportunity to educate others about their curls.</p>
<p>Genuine questions and conversations about natural curl care have been born from people asking about their hair, and curlies are usually happy to tell others what they know. As times are changing and acceptance of natural hair is growing, people are less likely to be bullied or harassed for their hair.  Acceptance of one's curls happens in its own time, so don't be worried if it takes a little while to get used to your natural hair.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<section class="comments embed" data-num-comments="0" id="comments"><a name="comments"></a><span></span></section>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
